Viewers all over the world.
Wherever you are...
wherever you are.
Distance is not a barrier.
Every familiar spirit. Every spirit that disturbs your career.
Every spirit that disturbs your life. I release you in the name of Jesus!
Be released!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Be released! Be released! Be released!
Don't go! Don't go away! Begin to confess your release!
Confess your release!
Don't go away. Confess your release!
I am released!
My business is released!
My finances are released!
I am released!
Confess your release! In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers anywhere you are, where can you go from His presence?
Right now begin to order anything that has to do with hardship
that has to do with hindrance.
That has to do with shortcoming.
That has to do with waste.
That has to do with setback.
Order them in your life!
Order them in your career!
Order them in your business!
Order them in your finances!
Order them. Begin to order them out!
Order them out in the name of Jesus!
"I order you out, you setback in my way!
I order you out, you shortcoming in my business"
You waste, you hardship, you poverty in my way.
In my career,
I order you out! Out of my life! Out of my way! Out of my way!
In Jesus Christ name!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch the screen by faith in Jesus name.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and say up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies.
from the Synagogue Church of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.